### CONTACT

**+249-999-0288-56** 

khalidmusa249@gmail.com

khartoum Sudan

#### **SKILLS**

html5

css3

**JavaScript** 

Bootstrap 5

Ajax

**JSON** 

Rect.js

React Native

Laravel

Flutter

Redux

Node.js

Express.js

JWT

MongoDB

GitHub

Git

SQL server

Linux

## **LANGUAGE**

English (advance)

Arabic(native)

# **KHALID MUSA**

#### **BUSINESS CONSULTANT**

Strong knowledge in **MERN** stack with vast experience in building web applications used **React.js** for client side, **Node.js**/Express.js for server side and **MongoDB** for database. Good in using **react/redux** to build user interface, good knowledge of state **store**, **middleware**, **action creator**, **reducer** and **container** 

#### **EDUCATION**

Sudan University Of Science And Technology

2015 - 2021

Bachelor Degree of electronics engineering

University of Khartoum - internship

jan 2021 - mar 2021 it support

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# CITS net for electronics services

jan 2022 - Present backend developer

- Develop highly interactive web applications utilizing JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, JSON, React JS and integrating Restful API's, external web services ensuring high performance on Mobile and Desktop. Provide SEO solutions for single page apps.
- Meet with project stakeholders discuss their vision, ideas and create compelling digital experiences.
- Manage the exchange of data between servers and users, develop backend components, and connect applications with other web services.

#### Freelancer

2020 - present Full-Stack developer

 designing user interactions on websites, developing servers and databases for website functionality and coding for mobile platforms.

# SOFT SKILLS

- analytical thinking
- Growth mind set
- Communication skills
- Team work

# PRTFOLIO LINKS

- https://khalidmusa.netlify.app/
  - https://github.com/khld-musa
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/khalid-musa-2024a1195